I am truly humbled to stand here and be
the head coach of the Miami Dolphins.
And I take a lot of pride [music] and
responsibility in that. And over the
last really 48 hours, I've had a lot of
time to reflect on that [music] and on
my journey and really where I came from
and how I got here. And the biggest
[music] thing that kept hitting me was
people. It's the players, it's the
coaches, and it's the families. And as I
really go through it, it's all those
lessons that I learned [music] in all
the places that I've been. I've had a
little bit different journey. I started
off coaching division 3 football, worked
my way up, went to the NFL, went back to
college football, became a head coach,
went back to the NFL, coordinated, and
now I'm here. But here's what I learned.
I started coaching division 3 football
where I [music] lined fields and cleaned
helmets and did laundry. And I loved it.
And what I learned was there's no job
too small. And that's what you're going
to get from me [music] every single day
cuz I learned how to work hard, like
really hard. And there's no replacement
for that. And [music] there won't be
here. And as I continued to move up, I
learned a lot from a lot of coaches. I
learned how to tell people the truth. I
learned how to tell players the truth,
[music] even if it wasn't they wanted to
hear.
I learned that it's it's okay to tell a
player you love them and to [music] pour
everything you can into them because
they're going to give it right back to
you. I learned how to be at my best when
things get hard. And I learned that when
things are good, that's when I got to
put my thumb on them. I learned what
it's like [music] to hold people to an
extreme level of accountability. I
learned what toughness is about. And I
learned how to grind from Hall of Fame
players. I learned that you got you
can't be afraid to coach guys. Every
good player wants to be told what to do
[music] and how hard to do it and you
can't back down cuz they all want to get
better. I learned about alignment and
that you have to have people's [music]
backs and you have to come together
which is a huge reason why I'm here
today with this guy right here. I
learned how to win and unfortunately
I've taken some losses. But what I've
learned I'm going to get back up every
single time and so are those [music]
people that are around me every single
day. And in doing that, I've kind of had
the core beliefs which we're going to
[music] instill in this football team,
into the players, and into this
organization. And the first one is
trust. And a lot of people use that word
lightly. I don't. And I think right now
in the world we live in, a lot of people
are slow to trust. It might be you. It
might be the players. And that's all
right cuz I'm going to earn it because
actions speak louder than words. I'm not
going to be able to I'm not going to be
want to sit here and talk a lot, but I'm
going to follow up with what I say I'm
going to do. And so are our team. The
next thing that I believe in is belief.
And I think this is really powerful
because it's a hard world right now
where people read stuff, they see stuff,
[music]
and you'd be surprised on how much
insecurity there is with players, with
coaches, with everybody. And I'm going
to let those players know that I believe
in them. And in [music] turn, what
you're going to see, you're going to see
a group of guys that believe in
themselves. And that becomes powerful
because when they start to believe in
themselves and our team starts to
connect with each other then look out
because you get that connection and then
we want to talk about accountability
then we have accountability and
accountability is love and it's an
extreme level of accountability and when
we build a standard and it starts to
become real the player will start to
hold themselves accountable but that's
going to start with me and the final
thing that I'm going to talk to him
about every single day is toughness
that's physically
That's [music] mentally. That's
everything that we do. And it's a
toughness that thrives on competition.
And it's a toughness that reflects the
people and the spirit of the city of
Miami. And that's what I'm most excited
about. [music]
And as we piece this thing together,
it's going to be it's going to take time
and there's going to be a lot of hard
work, but then it's going to be built
the right way. Like the foundation that
was laid for me when I was coaching
division 3 football and I learned how to
do things the [music] right way. And
that's how we're going to do it here
with a staff that's going to buy in and
with a group of men that are going that
are going to give everything that they
got. And I can look you guys in the eye
and tell you I cannot wait to get
started. And now really to my thank yous
to Mr. [music] Ross and your family.
Thank you for believing in me. I do not
take that lightly and I will do
everything I can for you and your
family.
[snorts]
To everybody in this group, from Sully
to Brandon to Troy to Dan to Danny to
Tom, thank you guys for believing in me
in [music] this process. You guys put me
through multiple interviews. We spent
time talking to each other. We had
multiple hard conversations on phone
calls, but it was always the
communication and it was awesome and I
appreciate it.
I want to thank all the coaches that
I've ever been around from WPI to Boston
College to every NFL team. And I want to
thank the players because I wouldn't be
here without those players. I learned
more from players than I've learned from
coaches. And I hope they feel that way
with me cuz the thing that I got into
this for [music] was changing lives. And
there's so many of those players that
changed my life, too. I want to thank
Matt Laflur and the Green Bay Packers.
The last two years have been two of the
best of my life. Uh he's a great
football coach. He's a great friend and
he's going to have continued great
success. I also want to thank those
players there. [music] In two years, we
got real close. I mean, really close.
The love, the connection, the support.
[music] It was hard to say goodbye to
those guys, but the phone calls and the
texts, you guys meant everything to me.
I love you. I wish you the best other
than when we come to Lambo next year.
I want to thank my family and this will
be
this is why I saved it for the end.
Hope and Leah.
Hope's laughing now, so that's good.
Leah, I thank you guys and I thank Gina.
And I can tell you this about Gina.
Gina's not into this so she can walk
around tell people that she's married to
the head coach of the Dolphins. She
doesn't care. All she cares about is us,
how I'm feeling, supporting me, and
doing everything she can for those kids.
I'm lucky today, too,
cuz I got my mom, my sister, brother
here today.
Flying here to be with me means
everything. And I thank him for that.
and for my real coach, my dad, my first
coach, who toughened me up
and was there for me.
I appreciate family more than you guys
have any idea. And like I told you guys,
I'm going to I'm going to wear it on my
sleeve at times. I'm going to be
passionate. I'm going to tell you how I
feel and you're going to get everything
I have. And to this city, to the fans,
this is a story organization, one of the
best in all sports. And you deserve a
winner. You guys deserve a winner. and I
am going to do everything in my power to
bring you guys that. I am so proud to be
here and I cannot wait to get started.
Thank you.